Here we go.
Three.
So conservative.
Not your style.
Are you afraid to bid?
Then you open first.
Hello, ladies.
Are you here on vacation?
Yes.
Do you have any plans for tomorrow?
How about I show you around?
No need.
Handsome boy.
Let me remind you.
Don't easily mess with our Shiya.
Be careful,
she might steal your soul.
When that happens,
your heart won't be able to take it.
To be seduced by you,
I'm more than willing.
I'm also more than willing.
Go away.
You're so cheesy.
Our Shiya likes clean-cut guys.
Then,
how about me?
Me.
You?
Yes, me.
Stop it.
See what you want to drink.
I'll go buy two bottles of liquor.
Ignore him.
What are you guys drinking?
Liquor.
Okay.
Then I'll drink too.
Shiya.
Today we celebrate.
To us.
Why leave me out?
Come, aren't you drinking?
Together. Come on.
Don't drink too much.
Mind your business.
You guys go ahead.
What's wrong?
Do you want to have
a man-to-man contest?
Bring it on.
Waiter,
bring us a drinking game set.
Coming.
It's been a long time since we played together.
Can you beat me this time?
Let's find out.
The usual.
Pei Song's tolerance...
It's terrible.
I'll go check.
It's okay.
Listen to me.
Come on,
they've been playing like this since they were kids.
Come on.
And,
Pei Ning wins every time.
You see,
even though Pei Song is good at almost everything else.
Come on!
But let me tell you,
when it comes to games,
Come on!
Pei Song is no good.
Come on.
Here we go again.
Push hard!
Come on!
Take him down!
Good.
I lost again, brother.
You think you're so tough.
Again?
Let's just drink.
Okay.
Waiter,
two bottles.
Coming right up.
Pei Song won.
This is...
a first.
Pei Ning,
what's wrong with you today?
Not feeling well?
Not feeling well.
This is a first.
Finally I win one.
First time.
I can still drink.
Come on.
Slow down.
You're a girl,
is it proper to drink this much?
Who are you?
Mind your own business.
You don't like drinking.
You don't understand the joy of alcohol.
Right, Shiya?
Let's go back and drink some more.
Yes.
Let's go.
Drink by yourself if you want.
Don't drag Shiya into this.
What do you know?
I'm trying to help you.
Be careful.
People say
that
wine brings out the truth.
Stupid.
You're drunk.
No.
Be careful.
I want more.
Pei Song,
I have something to talk to you about.
Sure.
I'm going to get some gas anyway.
Let's talk in the car.
What's wrong?
What do you want to talk about?
You and Pei Ning...
I was just playing around with him.
Pei Song,
you should know your brother's personality very well.
He is very sensitive.
After we get divorced,
should we still keep our distance?
What's wrong?
The brakes aren't working.
How could that be?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I have no signal on my phone.
Do you?
No.
The car is stuck too deep.
It's dangerous to keep driving.
And looking at the car,
it's not safe to stay inside either.
Let's find shelter from the wind.
Otherwise, we'll get hypothermia tonight.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
In case we can't get out,
we might need to make a fire when it gets cold at night.
I didn't expect you to know so much about wilderness survival.
Students,
when we are exploring outdoors,
the most important equipment includes
trekking poles.
It can help us
save energy during the climbing process.
And our climbing rope.
How to use the climbing rope?
Wrap one end around our waist,
and tie the other end to the carabiner.
It's very sturdy.
So when we encounter danger,
we must know our limits.
Give it to me.
There should be a cave not far ahead.
We can go there to take shelter tonight.
Then let's go.